https://pestcontrolcanada.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.pestontrolcanada.com.
This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.
It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address above.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
If we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email.
Webmanager@pestcontrolcanada.com
Top Viewed Posts
Assassin bug (the masked hunter) (8,485)
How to get rid of clothes moths (8,245)
picture-wing fly (5,986)
broad-nosed/short-snouted weevil (5,682)
Pseudoscorpion (5,050)
Elm Seed bugs (4,048)
Latest News and ArticlesThree Wild Mice Test Positive for HantavirusMarch 3, 2020 - 10:30 amA California man found a 70-pound beehive in his shed housing up to 150,000 beesFebruary 26, 2020 - 3:58 pmCalgarian cooks and eats pigeons — and says they’re deliciousFebruary 26, 2020 - 3:46 pmA swarm of nearly 40,000 bees attacked police responding to a single bee sting reportFebruary 26, 2020 - 3:33 pmLATEST PEST ID PHOTOGerman cockroachesDecember 10, 2020 - 11:43 amOrb weaving spiderDecember 10, 2020 - 11:39 amGiant ichneumon waspDecember 10, 2020 - 11:34 amMaggot of a muscoid flyDecember 10, 2020 - 11:27 amMature larva/prepupa of a rodent bot flyDecember 10, 2020 - 11:21 amPopular LinksSend Us Your Photo
Ask an Expert
Pest ID photos
Scroll to top
